

CONTACT

+33754196823

b.protasenko@gmail.com

Telegram: @probogdan

GitHub

<u>Linkedin</u>

Location: Brunoy, France

TECH SKILLS

- JavaScript/TypeScript
- React
- Redux Toolkit
- Node.is
- Express
- HTML, CSS
- Material UI
- REST API
- MongoDB
- GIT
- Jira

SOFT SKILLS

- Willingness to learn
- Attention to details
- Business communication skills
- Problem-solving skills

LANGUAGE

- Ukrainian (native)
- English (intermediate)

BOGDAN PROTASENKO

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

I'm a FullStack developer with knowledge in JavaScript, TypeScript, React and Node.js. I have a more than 8 years of experience leading large IT projects. Programming is my passion and I plan to achieve a high level of professionalism in it. My analitical skills help me to find effective solutions and successfully solve technical tasks.

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

O EXCHANGE&TRY | GitHub | Role: Creator, Developer

(Only for mobile as PWA App) The Mobile App facilitates the connection of sports enthusiasts for equipment exchange. <u>The Backend</u> of the App was developed using Node.js, Express, and MongoDB. <u>The Frontend</u> was created with TypeScript, React, and Redux Toolkit. Material UI was used for the design. For a detailed project overview and additional information, please refer to the description on GitHub.

An application for finding culinary recipes. The project is built using Vite, HTML, CSS, JS, REST API, and various libraries. My responsibilities in the project include designing the project structure, integration of developed modules into the final product and development of the functionality for the favorites page.

Simply Chocolate | GitHub | Role: Developer

Website with adaptive and responsive layout. My role: development of the "Our Products" section. Help in solving difficult tasks.

WORK EXPERIENCE

O 2011 - 2019 | Account project manager

CONTO LLC

Management of IT projects (ERP System with more than 100 key users)

- Team formation
- Project team management through the use Agile and SCRUM methodology
- Responsibility for project deadlines and budget compliance
- Interaction with Clients and Stakeholders
- Risk assessment and approval of risk management strategies

Achievements: Successful implementation of the company's largest projects, including <u>Luxoptica Ukraine</u>, <u>HarvEast Holding</u>, <u>Talisman Insurance</u>, <u>Alliance Oil Ukraine</u>

O 2007 - 2011 | Corporate manager

ABBYY

Sale IT projects

- Interaction with Stakeholders
- Proposal development with consideration of client needs
- Budget development and project finance management

Implementation IT projects

- Training the client's team to use the product
- Product customization for the Customer's project and technical support

EDUCATION

O 2023 - present time | Fullstack Developer

2001 - 2006 | Master of Computer Science

<u>Vasyl' Stus Donetsk National University</u> (Faculty of Information and Applied Technologies)